MUHAMAD PARHAN MAULANA

Frontend Developer (React)

+6283836319218 | mparhanmaulana17@gmail.com www.handev.my.id

SUMMARY

A programmer with over 1 year of experience adept at developing frontend web and mobile software integrated with APIs. Having completed 10+ real projects and personal projects using the React.js, Next.js, and React Native tech stack.

EDUCATION

2021 - 2024 SMK YASBAM KOTA BOGOR

Teknik Komputer Dan Jaringan

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023 | Praktik Kerja Lapangan | Pusat Pengembangan ASN

2023 - Sekarang | Freelance

- Web and application development. Utilizing React.js, Next.js, React Native, or WordPress.
- Feature addition, debugging.

SKILLS

· HTML, CSS

JAVASCRIPT

TYPESCRIPT

REACT JS

NEXT JS

- STATE MANAGEMENT
- REDUX TOOLKIT
- ZUSTAND
- REACT QUERY
- TAILWINDCSS

PORTOFOLIO

- · www.fashiotrendz.handev.my.id
- www.threads.handev.my.id
- · more di: www.handev.my.id